Hi everyone,and welcome
to “Shipped,”
our quarterly look at what we've been
building across the Sinch platform.
And more importantly,
what does this mean for our customers?
This quarter we’ll focus on one of the
biggest shifts happening in our industry,
AI moving from experimental
into real world customer experiences.
I'm Roshni, Senior Director of Product
Marketing at Sinch,
and joining me today is Jonathan,
our Messaging VP of Product.
Thanks, Roshni.
So with the shift you mentioned towards
AI powered customer experiences
the two things that matter most are:
how you reach people, and whether they trust
what they're actually receiving
And Sinch handles both at a global scale.
So today, we're unveiling the three
most recent releases to help you deploy
AI comms confidently and quickly.
Okay. Thanks, Jonathan.
Let's get into it.
Starting with a new release
for Sinch tools.
Every time you add a new
capability to a project,
developers have to switch
between documentation, portals, testing
tools, and application code.
This friction adds up quickly.
Sinch tools is here to
help remove that friction.
It is a suite of AI-native
developer capabilities
that help teams build,
test, and deploy on Sinch
within the tools they're
already using today.
Developers can pick and choose
what tools they need
based on their use case.
At the foundation is MCP,
which connects AI coding environments
like Claude Code and Cursor
directly to Sinchs’ live API service.
When an agent generates code
or drafts and integration,
it’s working from real requirements
and current product definitions.
And then we have Skills,
which provide the structured
product knowledge and
implementation expertise.
Parameters are configured correctly,
the recommended patterns are built in,
and the common edge cases
are already accounted for.
Instead of guessing how you should
build these products,
agents operate from a trusted
product intelligence.
Once this code is generated,
CLI allows products
to test, validate, and troubleshoot
directly from the terminal
before anything reaches production.
Language-native SDKs
accelerate implementation by eliminating
repetitive boilerplate, and providing
production-ready building blocks.
And finally,
we have Functions - which serves
as the execution layer
for event-driven workflows.
Whether it's sending an SMS
when a user signs up, escalating a
critical alert through voice, or triggering
verifications during authentications,
Functions connects business events
to customer interactions automatically.
Together, these tools create
a complete developer workflow
that moves from idea to production faster.
AI agents and developers
working from the same trusted foundation.
Next up, Jonathan is going to tell us
about the next release,
Sinch Chat and Sinch Push.
So you've built your agent,
it can handle conversations,
and it knows your product,
but for customers
to actually interact with the agent,
it needs to be on the channels
they already use.
Sinch Chat and Sinch Push
give you two owned channels
to meet customers right where they are.
Sinch Chat turns your app or
your website into a
live two-way conversation.
Your AI agent handles the repetitive stuff,
your team handles the moments
that actually move the needle.
The customer never has to leave
the session to get an answer.
Sinch Push is the re-engagement side.
So, someone drops off mid-session,
Push reaches them
directly on their device.
It's opted-in, highly cost effective,
and there's no middleman.
To bring us home,
I'll hand it back over to Roshni
to tell us about our next release,
Sinch Mailgun Inspect for
Salesforce Marketing Cloud Next.
More and more teams are using AI
to create email content,
which is great for productivity,
but it can increase the risk of triggering
spam filters, missing broken
links, and failing accessibility checks.
Now that Mailgun Inspect is
directly available inside
Salesforce Marketing Cloud Next,
you can preview emails across
more than 100 devices and email clients,
without ever leaving the Salesforce UI.
Generic desktop and mobile previews
give you a visual
representation
of how email is expected to render.
Mailgun Inspect shows you
exactly how it renders
on the email clients your
subscribers are using today,
and both in light and dark mode,
You can open up any preview
at full resolution,
compare clients side-by-side,
make a change to the email,
and watch it re-render in real time.
In addition,
it offers link and image validation,
accessibility checks, and spam analysis.
And because it's now all available
in Sales Force Marketing Cloud Next,
teams can complete the entire
QA process where they're already
building their campaigns,
spending less time exporting the code,
switching tools,
and moving between tabs.
You can find Mailgun Inspect
on the Salesforce App Exchange today.
So that's it for our three releases.
We've brought you solid infrastructure
to build on,
channels to deploy through,
and a quality layer to keep it trustworthy
once it's out in a wild.
You'll find a full breakdown of
documentation and more,
everything we've covered today,
at sinch.com/shipped
And we'll meet you back
here next quarter
to see what's shipped at Sinch.
Thanks for watching,
everybody - ‘till next time.